

Ahren Wagner





wagnerahren@gmail.com

https://www.linkedin.com/in/ahrenwagner/

Cell: +27 72 089 0762

SKILLS

FRAMEWORKS AND LANGUAGES

- React, Next.js and TypeScript
- Version control and collaboration using GitHub/BitBucket
- Design libraries and tools such as TailWindCSS and Chakra UI
- Using AI tools such GitHub Copilot and ChatGPT
- Miscellaneous Google Document Suite, Microsoft Suite, OBS

SOFTWARE PROJECTS

I'm enthusiastic about connecting with fellow developers, exploring and building projects with modern technologies such as Express, Firebase and Three.js while working with Al tools such as CoPilot and ChatGPT



COMMUNICATION

- Fluent in English with strong reading and writing skills. Solid understanding

 Afrikaans in spoken and written form
- Excellent interpersonal skills, able to **listen** and incorporate input from others while working in collaborative environments
- Experienced with **Jira** , **Confluence** and **Trello** to implement **agile** methods such as the Kanban method

PERSONAL INTERESTS

- Enthusiastic artist in my spare time, focusing on pencil, watercolour and film photography
- Brazilian Jiu Jitsu

References on request

PROFILE

I am a **React Software Developer** with a strong focus on **front end development** and design, with experience and interest in various full stack technologies.

My background is in education, having studied mathematics for several years before completing a **Bachelors in Education(Senior Phase)** and transitioning into software development, initially by teaching coding courses before working as a software developer. I'm always interested in the human aspect of software development, whether it's in the design and layout of a website, or the choices made in tailoring a project to best fit a client's needs.

My aim for the future is to focus on front end development, incorporating my enjoyment of design and art to create accessible, performant and engaging experiences for users.

EXPERIENCE

FRONTEND DEVELOPER SECURITEASE -FEB-2024-PRESENT

Working in FinTech for various banks in Australia, New Zealand and South Africa. With a strong focus on creating robust, well tested accessible user interfaces using **React, TanStack** Software, with **Jest** and **PlayWright,** while regularly engaging in code review and documentation creation

FRONTEND DEVELOPER ACCENTURE SONG - NOV 2023-FEB 2024

Recruited by Accenture Song to work on client facing portals for Audi UK, using React, Styled Components and **Jest** and **React-Testing-Library**.

FREELANCE SOFTWARE DEVELOPMENT - FEB 2023 - NOV 2023

ModulR - Developing various projects using Express.js, Next.js , TailwindCSS. Using tools such as TanStackQuery and Zod to create type-safe and robust code.

REACT DEVELOPER AT MEETINGPAL (WEBINTELLECT) - APRIL 2022 - JAN 2023

Using **React, Javascript, TypeScript, Meteor** and **MongoDB** I assisted in developing features required to adhere to remotely managing body corporate meetings.

CODECOACH AT CODESPACE - JULY 2021- APRIL 2022

Developed courses and documentation for **JavaScript, HTML, CSS** and Sonic Pi,. While also teaching programming courses the languages mentioned, to a wide variety of learners with differing technological backgrounds and ages. Responsibilities included recording videos, creating projects and tasks, teaching classes and updating curriculum courses.

EDUCATION STUDENT AND MASTER MATHS TUTOR - 2015-2021

- Master Maths from Feb 2015 to Jan 2017. Teaching Maths and Science to high school learners.
- Student teacher for 6 months during course of studies during which I taught classes and aided teachers fulfil various responsibilities.

EDUCATION

- Bachelor of Education Intermediate and Senior Phase at Stellenbosch University 2017-2020
- BsC Maths and Physics at Stellenbosch University 2013-2014
- Self Study, Peer learning and Projects 2018- Present